A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Corporation, Board of Trustees, Working Files FA998
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Corporation, Board of Trustees, Working Files
1967-1997
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
FA998
16.67 Cubic Feet 18 boxes - 12 standard record storage cartons, 2 document boxes and one half-document box.
18 boxes - 12 standard record storage cartons, 2 document boxes and one half-document box.
Conditions Governing Access
Material more than 25 years old is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 130-6-U
Arrangement
Chronological
Scope and Contents
Contains: Board of Trustees, Executive Committee, and select documentation of Budget Committee, Building and Real Estate and Finance Committee including correspondence, minutes, agendas and associated background materials.
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1967 January 30-1969 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 1-12)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1969 October 22-1970 March 24 (Box 2, Folder 1-5)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1970 May 11 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1970 July 8-1972 January 18 (Box 4, Folder 1-14)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1972 March 16-1973 May 3 (Box 5, Folder 1-17)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1973 May 2-1974 July 25 (Box 6, Folder 1-11)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1974 October 7-1975 July 22 (Box 7, Folder 1-13)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1975 October 23-1976 August 4 (Box 8, Folder 1-18)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1976 July 22-1978 May 16 (Box 9, Folder 1-24)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1978 May 16-1980 May 7 (Box 10, Folder 1-25)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1980 June 11-1981 July 29 (Box 11, Folder 1-19)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1981 July 29-1982 October 5 (Box 12, Folder 1-20)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1982 November 30 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1983 January 20 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1989 November 3-1990 November 1 (Box 13, Folder 3-7)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1991 January 23-October 17 (Box 13, Folder 8-15)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted from scholarly acccess - Open in 2017
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1992 February 21-June 18 (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
  Restricted from scholarly acccess - Open in 2018
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1992 June 18-November 6 (Box 14, Folder 1-7)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1993 January 27-November 17 (Box 14, Folder 8-21)
  Restricted from scholarly acccess - Open in 2019
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1994 March 23 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  Restricted from scholarly acccess - Open in 2020
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1994 March 23-November 16 (Box 15, Folder 1-14)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1995 March 22-November 15 (Box 15, Folder 15-19)
  Restricted from scholarly acccess - Open in 2021
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1996 March 20-June 13 (Box 15, Folder 20-22)
  Restricted from scholarly acccess - Open in 2022
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Working Files, 1997 November 12 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  Restricted from scholarly acccess - Open in 2023